S KAVITHA

1/1011, 4th street, thiruvengadam nagar, vadakupattu. Ch-600100. MOB# 9962305871 / 8072949127 kavitha.sekar151189@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Skytech Engineering, Chennai — *Accountant*

Apr2010 to Mar2012

1.Responsible For All The Accounting Activities,Labour Wages Calculation,Managing day-to-day expenses with creating balance sheets,tracker.

Orion water treatment Pvt.Ltd; Chennai — Accounts & Admin officer

Apr2012 to Sep2014

- 1.Responsible for all the accounting activities, managing bank accounts & Office Administration.
- 2. Responsible for data maintenance both excel and Tally ERP.
- 3. Assisting senior accountants in their works.

Anico International, Chennai — *Accountant*

Oct 2014 To March 2019

- 1.Responsible for all the accounting activities, cash flow statement generation both project and day-to-day basis, Labour, supplier and customer management. Responsible For Processing Payments To Supplier, wages to laborers and customer payments, & administrative work
- 2. Maintaining data in MsExcel, Tally and in manual modes.

Croma, Chennai — Assistant Accounts & Admin

Nov 2020 To Jul 2022

- 1. Head cashier role
- 2.To maintain all the accounts in SAP,.Maintaining mode of payments "GL maintaining in SAP"
- 3. Admin roles such as , "To maintain housekeeping, valet parking, securities, finance persons & cashiers.
- 4. Managing permissions and leaves of the employees, monthly vendor payments, approval of salary slips of admins.
- 5.Resolving day to day customer related issues , billing related issues , cash deposits.

SKILLS

MS OFFICE - Excel, Word
TALLY
SAP
Rusiness Communication

Career Summary

Above 10 years of work experience in both accounting and office administration most preferably in a manufacturing & Retail industry.

A keen and energetic accounting graduate with broad knowledge Tallyerp9 and accounting concepts strategies.

Familiar With Accounting Procedures And Practices.

Proficient in communication with multitasking and problem solving with an experience in labour, vendor and customer management.

EDUCATION

- 1. A Graduate in Bachelor's Of Commerce (Bcom) with 59% from Madras University.
- 2.Higher secondary (Class12) with 55% from board of intermediate education.
- 3.Secondary school (Class 10) with 52% from board of secondary education.